<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HIGH RISE</string>
    <string name="default_pressagainmsg">Press again to go back.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="network_disable">No internet.</string>


    <string name="tip_title1">Do your research!</string>
    <string name="tip_title2">Be prepared to show your work!</string>
    <string name="tip_title3">First impressions count!</string>
    <string name="tip_title4">Keep your answers\nconcise and focused!</string>
    <string name="tip_title5">Prepare a list of references!</string>
    <string name="tip_title6">Recruit a friend!</string>
    <string name="tip_title7">Line up your questions!</string>
    <string name="tip_title8">End the interview\nwith a good impression!</string>

    <string name="tip_text1">Do your homework and research the employer and the industry. Using the company’s website,
        social media posts, and recent press releases will provide a solid understanding of the company’s goals and how
        your background makes you a great fit.
    </string>
    <string name="tip_text2">During the interview, you will likely be asked about specific work you’ve completed in
        relation to the position. Think of work you’ve done in past jobs, clubs, or volunteer positions that show you
        have experience and success doing the work they require.
    </string>
    <string name="tip_text3">Don’t forget the little things—shine your shoes, make sure your nails are clean and tidy,
        and check your clothes for holes, stains, pet hair, and loose threads. Display confident body language and a
        smile throughout.
    </string>
    <string name="tip_text4">Your time with each interviewer is limited so be mindful of rambling. Practicing your
        answers beforehand can help keep you focused.
    </string>
    <string name="tip_text5">Your interviewers might require you to submit a list of references before or after your
        interview. Having a reference list prepared ahead of time can help you quickly complete this step to move
        forward in the hiring process.
    </string>
    <string name="tip_text6">Practicing your answers out loud is an incredibly effective way to prepare. Say them to
        yourself or ask a friend to help run through questions and answers.
    </string>
    <string name="tip_text7">Come to the interview with some intelligent questions for the interviewer that demonstrate
        your knowledge of the company as well as your serious intent. Interviewers always ask if you have any questions,
        and no matter what, you should have one or two ready.
    </string>
    <string name="tip_text8">A positive end to the interview is another way to ensure your success. Be courteous and
        allow the interview to end on time. Restate any strengths and experiences that you might not have emphasized
        earlier.
    </string>
</resources>